That Citi is the most romantic short term plan,
it is up to the pimples, that is, in our options the
family gets money, a death
benefit transfer online for free,
okay, there is no
maturity, no premium, operator, do
you have any money back plan, okay,
only death benefit, which we
select the duration, if the
city dies during the session, then the person will
get the money, if we win, then the person will
not get any money, character can take it from 18 years
to 60 years, minimum
annual income is five black right now in online,
qualification should be graduation, should be
graduate, in income proof, if you were
working, had subscribed for the last,
politicians, if you want to edit photo debit Krishna, then
cancel cheque will be uploaded,
okay,
airplane mode can be maintained, plus let me
tell you what kind of fee slipper type update this is,
we are covering death due to any
reason, whether it is natural death,
central death or due to any disease,
then side death or murder, okay
We are breaking you into girl type updates and staying
on the side, what happens is that if not, but if the
school is folded, then you
get 60% of the love you have given in a year, okay,
if after a year there is a suicide
attempt, you will get the entire life
cover, if you have taken a loan of fifty lakhs, then you will get
50 lakhs, okay,
this is only in case of suicide, even if a
college student dies, then you get the full
benefit, that is, the company itself will
do that, that the
money is covered, terminal
English, terminal illness or Chandra tension,
incurable disease like advanced stage
of cancer, hospitalization is not more than six months, then do we pay for it, do we
receive the medical bill, do we pay the full amount,
okay,
this subscribe to How to
Win a Web Server Not to Raghbir and
subscribe to the channel, we cover the
customer, I can take cover with this,
or do we not cover
it, if you add minimum two lakhs, I
can add my time apart from this, I will
not cover more than that  So
if you welcome the Support Karo tablet due to some
critical then first you will get it once the
critical is over and secondly
you tell it to minimize it
in your purse, what happens sir, if the
policy holder has taken a Support Karo plan of 50 lakhs
and has taken an additional
left ventricle plan of 50 lakhs, God forbid, how can
everyone die due to an accident, okay the
nominee gets double the money in that case,
50 lakhs accidental and up to 50 lakhs normal
plan, the entire time is very less and right now